[

](https://uwncnm.org/)

Menu

Search

Search 

Close this search box.

PRIVACY POLICY
==============

UWNCNM recognizes the importance of protecting information we may collect from visitors to our site. Our policy is to use the information we acquire from visitors to our sites for internal purposes only, and we maintain appropriate security measures to keep this information private.

Users can visit the site without revealing any information about themselves. If one chooses to give us personal information via the Internet for the purposes of correspondence, processing an order, special site features and applications, or providing a subscription to a publication, then it is our intent to let you know how we will use such information. Occasionally, stored email addresses may be used for internal correspondence with our user base; however, this information will never be shared intentionally with third-parties.

If users tell us that they do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact, we will respect those wishes. We do keep track of the domains from which people visit us. We analyze this data for trends, insights and statistics, and then we discard it. Information may be maintained on an opt in basis only for receipt of communication and products from United Way. Only users of 13 years or older can opt in.

UWNCNM takes precautions to keep the user information disclosed to us secure, and such information will not be disclosed to third parties for commercial purposes. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect. UWNCNM uses SSL encryption for all financial transactions to protect personal information.

**User Agreement**

If you have any questions about this User Agreement, **[contact UWNCNM](mailto:info@uwncnm.org)**. If you do not agree with these terms of this User Agreement, you may not use the site. UWNCNM reserves the right to change this User Agreement at any time without notice.

Help every family and every child in our community have a stronger, brighter future.

BE IN THE KNOW
--------------

Sign up for our emails and stay informed about how we work with partners and supporters like you to strengthen our community.

* © 2023

We use cookies to improve your experience on our site. To find out more, read our privacy policy and cookie policy. By continuing to browse this site, you agree to our use of cookies.  
To learn more, please read our [privacy policy](https://uwncnm.org/privacy-policy) I'm okay with that

Manage consent

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. These cookies ensure basic functionalities and security features of the website, anonymously.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-analytics | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Analytics". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-functional | 11 months | The cookie is set by GDPR cookie consent to record the user consent for the cookies in the category "Functional". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookies is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Necessary". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-others | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Other. |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-performance | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Performance". |
| viewed\_cookie\_policy | 11 months | The cookie is set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin and is used to store whether or not user has consented to the use of cookies. It does not store any personal data. |

Functional

 Functional

Functional cookies help to perform certain functionalities like sharing the content of the website on social media platforms, collect feedbacks, and other third-party features.

Performance

 Performance

Performance cookies are used to understand and analyze the key performance indexes of the website which helps in delivering a better user experience for the visitors.

Analytics

 Analytics

Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.

Advertisement

 Advertisement

Advertisement cookies are used to provide visitors with relevant ads and marketing campaigns. These cookies track visitors across websites and collect information to provide customized ads.

Others

 Others

Other uncategorized cookies are those that are being analyzed and have not been classified into a category as yet.

SAVE & ACCEPT

BE IN THE KNOW
--------------

Sign up for our emails and stay informed about how we work with partners and supporters like you to strengthen our community.
